<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For you my dear</title>
    <description>Just a simple site for you by my, for our adventures, and my thoughts so you may know me better.
</description>
    <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://foryoumydear.nl/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 20:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 20:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A quiet weekend with ups and downs</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;19-10 - Firday&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey Cutie, It has been a while since you came to my place on a friday. Never the less I enjoyed our date night eventhough my driving on the bike was rough.
Again I will prommise you yo change that as I want to be around you longer, Hopefully youll be in the back once more I really do enjoy it.
Either way our trip to body worlds was great it was interesting and you seemed to have fun aswell. Our dinner well it was food lets keep it a that. For a place at the Dam in Amsterdam
you would think it would turn out a bit better than it did. At home we almost went straight to bed as we were quite tired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sorry for upsetting you though, the last thing I want to do is to hurt you in any way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;20-10 - Saturday&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up late, as leaving the bed was quite hard to do with all the cuddles that we had. But eventually we did and after we had quick breakfast, and you called your mom we went out for a run!
Even though we did split up because of our speed difference I still had a super great time with you, we did even run 6.51K not too bad at all! quite happy with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From here it was time for lunch and we started our wall map project, we made it half way through the map before we decided on dinner with wine.
Now the hard part but also the most beautifull part of the weekend, We shared so much of our selfs we grew so much closer, And again you will be safe with me for as long as we are together.
There is nothing I would not do to keep you safe. But then I also realize you are a tough cookie so I will have to balance it out, And manage my self not to be too much..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure we will find our way together as we have done many times now, Even with the map we seemed to work together pritty well as we seem to do in the kitchen too.
Time for a movie then a netflix origional “beirut” we did not finish it as you fell asleep while I was laying against you feeling so close and content with us. quite a magical moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In bed we talked some more before we fell asleep with more cuddles. It is seriously something I cant get enough of your warm hug your comfort and smile afterwards as you lean your head
back resting it on my arms for support so I can kiss you all over your face. These little moments that we share are the ones that stick the most.
The best thing you said this day: “We just have to marry before I leave” It wont solve the problem but it shows how much you love me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;21-10 - Sunday&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sunday we woke up at a reasonable time with cuddles, you inmediatly wanted to go work. You must have worked for atleast 3 hours while I was at my parents too in the mean time.
They were expecting you actually, But doesnt matter we discussed a lot also about us, upcomming christmas, the birthday party of Lex, the mess at my moms place I have to clear up with them
And many more things. Once home you were still busy working so I let you to it. After your work we went on an got back to our project. it is now hanging complete at the wall.
Time for our travell pictures I will make those this week somewhere. We finished up beirut afterwards then time for dinner some chillaxing with netflix and it wass off to bed again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/WallMap/ourmap-groundpaint.png&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;Map&quot; data-title=&quot;Wall map with ground paint!&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;park&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/WallMap/ourmap-groundpaint.png&quot; alt=&quot;Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/WallMap/ourmap-done.png&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;Map&quot; data-title=&quot;Wall map done!&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;park&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/WallMap/ourmap-done.png&quot; alt=&quot;Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;22-10 - Monday&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, my first day of a week where i yet have to get all my plans for I am having a few das off between jobs. Next monday I will start in Amsterdam, thanks to you I made this happen.
I am really gratefull, it really is a good step forward. I hope soon you will manage to do the same I am really supporting you like a cheerleader even though I seem to have put a selfish request
at your end. This morning I had to drop you off at the station again. And somehow you packing your stuff on a sunday and leaving on a monday still is not something I am used to. And I secretly hope
I never will aswell rather have you stay, but I know that day will come sooner or later the day we have our own first place thogether. Lets see how we manage our 3 weeks sleep over in December,
how our routine will come together. If our cooking, and our project is anything to go by it is that we can work together, so we should be able to work it out together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To wrap up this tremendous weekend here some current countdowns:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5 more weekends till December&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;8 more weekends till our early christmas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;8 more weekends till your vacation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;9 more weekends till my vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our list of 2019 travell plans:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open plans: Peru&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekends away: England, Austria&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;September: Malaysia, Cambodja&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most important of all:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 more days till I see you again!
&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/22/normal-weekend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/22/normal-weekend.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The weekend we went to Paris</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;5-10 - To France!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lovely weekend (5-10 / 7-10) we went to Paris, we had multiple things to celebrate. First of course our second month together, And
my 28th birthday! On Friday evening I picked you up straight from work a bit too early but you managed to get to a call in the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this we moved trough the tough traffic in the Netherlands onwards to Belgium. Over al it was a pleasant drive we stopped once at a
gas station not only to get gas, but also some food and to pee. After this quick break we went onwards to Paris where we arrived a bit too early
at the Airb&amp;amp;b you had booked for us. After some calling with our host we were she came to open up the door for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were greeted with a huge tennis hall behind the house and a interesting smell we had to go upstairs to a lovely room where we were explained
all the facilities. By this time it was around 00:00 so we went to bed to wake up the next morning to go to the inner city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;6-10 - Paris&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up and did our thing as this is our first travel together its still getting a bit used to how we are during it all.
Turns out not too bad! We were woken up by the old cat that was surprisingly loud for her age. We did our thing got dressed got our bags and
walked out to the nearest tram station. Here we got some good old cash just in case we needed some, And faced our first minor challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tramhalte.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Looking over the hill.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tramhalte.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tram.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;You in the tram.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tram.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying the tram tickets was a bit fiddly but somehow we managed without a fight, but did end up with fresh puke under our shoes!
After this we travelled the wrong way in the tram, nothing a quick turnaround could not fix!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once at the destination of our first stop we had some lovely breakfast! which was of course a french crepe.
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610crepe.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Ah CREPE!.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610crepe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Crepe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
After which it was time for museum number one! which had a main exhibition about a girl and a unicorn. Maybe its a french thing but it was way more quiet then I am used to from any
museum. But after seeing the entire place we went on to the next stop a another museum, This time about about arabism. This was quite
a large museum divided over multiple levels of a 10 story building. The only downside was that it was mostly in french, with we both dont speak
and read so it was mainly looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it was time to explore the city itself and its hotspots. We went to sit near the Notre dame, for a lovely talk and some cuddles and ofcourse a lovely photo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610us.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Us looking at the Notre Dame.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610us.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;our travell map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this we went looking for the lock bridge, turnsout the cleaned it up! not to worry it was a bonus to the trip we went onwards inside the
Notre Dame where we witnessed the starting of a church session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610notredame.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;You in the Notre Dame.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610notredame.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We left this quite quickly and we got some delicious ice cream and ate this while looking over the river Seine. After I romantically tried to remove some ice cream from your face it was time for a quick bathroom break while we went to the Eifel tower!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once at the Eifel tower, We had to go trough a security checkpoint where we both got pooped on by a bird unfortunately, but you brought wet wipes and saved the day! After this, Yet another line to wait in this time to get the tickets to get into the tower. We wanted to take the stairs but were suddenly greeted with a closing ticket desk, Turns out that the stairs are not open to climb up after 21:00. We had to go to a different line to get the tickets for the elevator. In hind sight this was a batter idea any way But before we got there another checkpoint and up we go! time to get a great view and some lovely pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tower.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Us in the top of the tower.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610tower.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Us in the top of the tower.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we saw all of that we had the challenge of a hungry tummy. Which make me a bit more grumpy than it should, You compromised for me to get something quick and easy in a nice restaurant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;7-10 - Brussels and Home&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All good things come to an end even a lovely weekend to Paris, Though it sees that we have to go back here once more :) if only for Asterix parc haha! After packing our stuff leaving our Airb&amp;amp;b we set out for ofcourse a baguette and some pasteries before we headed to Barneveld. On the way I suggested we stopped at Brussels since it was on our way back home anyway and so we got some dinner here ans ofcourse a selfie:
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610brussels.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Us in Brussels.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris/paris0610brussels.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Us in Brussels.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now really time to get home and feed the cats, go to bed and the next morning to work for the both of us!
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/04/paris.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/04/paris.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sneaking out at 5!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;19-09 - Den Hauge&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This evening was quite something, we went on our first date night! Its a fun thing to do with you so the weekends will get a different purpose and this
will be extra special moments not to forget, As you shall soon be read. We started of  with watching a movie in the pathe in Den Hauge it was called ‘Johny English strikes again’
After which we went to the city to get something to eat. After much deliberation and choiche stress we settled for Havannah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quite a nice place for a bin of nachos and some drinks before it turns into a night club, where you dont really want to go to!
Here is where it got interesting, I still had to go home but it was getting quite late! So we walked to your home where you invited me in. In hindsight very sweet but not very practical
as you are not allowed to have visitors to stay over (well manly ones atleast) We settled upon some rest for the both of us which resulted in us waking up at 5 to sneak me out of the house
in order to drive home!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;23-09/25-9 - Barneveld&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rest of the weekend went on quite normally, You stayed over till tueseday morning which was quite a nice change actually.
&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/09/25/sneaking-out.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/09/25/sneaking-out.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Short stories.</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;31-08/02-09 - Barneveld&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here it is our first complete weekend together! We did not do much, But we did get to know eachother more intimatly. With this our daily routins that we have.
You also saw my parents for the first time, But not yet my sister she was working. After all of this I brought you home on a 2.5 hour drive the scenic route just
to spend more time with you. We then had ramen in China town!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;05-09 - Barneveld&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the date of our first month together, Unfortunatly this fell on a wednesday but we will celebrate this later in the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;07-09/09-09 - Barneveld&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weekend of our first mont aniversairy, It did not go completly smooth but we are still getting used to one another.
We went for a lovely dinner here in Barneveld at the Hebbert not a special place but it was nice enough. Next time I will have to up the game on this!
Any how we went home, had wine and went to bed and woke up super late!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than that you worked, I did my laundryand other stuff and in the evening we watched a movie! The following sunday was a bit rough but in the end we had a great day!
We had coffee, ice cream rolls, kimci and i dropped you off at home, Still not getting used to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/09/09/first-weekend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/09/09/first-weekend.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A wild few days to start</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;16-08 - Your kitchen (again)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems to be a trend to be at your kitchen, but not too worry it will all change soon! This is the start of a few days where we will see eachother before you go to France on a mini vacation on your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this day we cuddled, cooked, and talked some more! We made plans to go on vacation together in December which is a big thing to do within our first month. But I am glad we did.
It really gives me a point to look forward to. Also as wierd as my mind is it seems like for aslong as you dont cancell that we are great, This first weeks have been full of insecurities about echother.
But we should let them be and focus on the more positive side of things. When will this vacation be? well we both have different go dates our vacation planning will as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- 21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;December&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; You fly to Malaysia&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- 26&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;December&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;I fly to Hong kong&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- 28&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;December&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Quick day trip to Maccau for me&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- 31&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;December&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;I fly to Malaysia to be with you once more after &lt;b&gt;9&lt;/b&gt; days of not seeing you&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- 5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;January&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;We will fly home together&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also discussed our first INSTA appearance, Quite a few plans we had for this picture. But also quite a impact so it would seem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;18-08 / 19-08 - Lots of little things&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did a lot of little things these few days, we booked our flight tickets from Malaysia to Amsterdam and we took a few lovely pictures. Here is one of them:
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/park1908.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;Park&quot; data-title=&quot;Our first picture together!&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;park&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/park1908.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Park&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my parents had a lot to say about this picture in the positive feadback kind of way but still haha, the have this one hanging for now in their home to remind them of us :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;22-08 - Ballonfiesta&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Wednesday you came to Barneveld just to watch some balloons rize with me! it was a super lovely evening. Definatly will go here with you again next year! As memmory servers well,
You even stayed over for the first time, But also it was your first time on a bike with back padle breaks. Which did not go completly smooth at the traffic light but we managed to avoid all accidnents.
Last but not least you like my fish dinner that i made for you, and we did not sleep very much mostly talks and cudles!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/21/a-wild-start.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/21/a-wild-start.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The day you and I became us</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;05-08 - Your kitchen&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This day marks the beginnig of our official relation ship status. You could call this date number 4, We were once more at your kitchen table.
Here you sat on my lap, and I had to ask were we now official?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer from you was&lt;b&gt; yes! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You had one remark though werent we yester day already? I opted to be sure today instead as I felt the same, but did not want to make the assumption. Silly me ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wich day you choose to mark as the beginning of our wonderfull relation, I dont want to loose you anymore!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/05/it-is-official.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/05/it-is-official.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Domburg Zeeland</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;25-07 - Domburg!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This day is special, not because we are seeing eachother for the third time but this is the day of our first kiss. This was for me a mega magicall moment, But before we got there we had a long ride ahead.
I doubted to take you by car or bike. After a good debate we chose the bike and i am super glad that we did in hindsight because of the traffic. I picked you up and drove with you to a museum Neeltje jans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best partk of the museum was definatly the sea lions!
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/domburg/date2sealions.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;Domburg&quot; data-title=&quot;Sniffing sealions.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/domburg/date2sealions.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Domburg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some more walking about we sat there on a nice beach looking towards the dam that is keeping the netherlands dry! This spot is where our first kiss happend.
Unfortunatly we had to go it was closing time for the park, but not too worry we had more plans. We went to drive to domburg and had dinner there and went to once again a beach!
Here ofcourse more kisses and hugs happend while we enjoyed the view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/domburg/date2theview.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;Domburg&quot; data-title=&quot;The view at the beach!&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/domburg/date2theview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Domburg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end I got you home safe and sound happy and full of love, such a great day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/04/domburg.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/04/domburg.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tinder</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;25-07 - Tinder!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is our beginning not very glamerous, or a funny story but as most people these days we met on the internet. The dating app tinder was our choice.
For me it started with seeing your profile, after reading it I super liked you. From here the waiting started to see if you would like me too.
Why I liked you, well your photos, and the “not quite the typical 😉” helped together with as you now know my thing for asians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You swiped on the other hand as you have told me because of my motor cycle (not mainly but it gave the final say)! Either way I am not complaining about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;28-07 - The day we should have met&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah I know, I should have met you this day. If i knew what I know today that you would steal my heart so quickly as you did later on. Unfortunatly we both had plans
And by the time I was done after a hactic day, it was 23:00. My chanche gone and you in bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;29-07 - Our first date?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well I managed to meet you a day later and seriously I am not regretting doing this. Our intention was to meet as frieds to build a great friendship, Secretly I was also open for more.
I just had to meet you, our conversations were so interesting and captivating. you sounded non typical indeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so we did around 15:30, well that was the plan you were late ;), But it now seems that it was also a bit my fault for parking at the wrong store.
Either way all was forgiven the moment I saw your face with a huge smile bouncing over the crossing. We hugged and we go t you situated on the bike for our ride to the beach!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we were at Scheveningen, we walked up the pier, the beach and onto a port for the life guards. Here we sat down at the end of the strorm breaker for quite a while.
We talked (well mostly I did) about lots of things, so much so it was time for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/tinder2907.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;tinder&quot; data-title=&quot;We sat here quite a while.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/tinder2907.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tinder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got Indonesian food, probably because we talked about it in one shape or form, Not sure how that happend any longer. But here I sat across you the first time i propperly got to take a look at you.
Ad boy did I fell in love with those brown eyes, Problem was we were there for friendsip! After some staring some more talking I got you home after we got lost. And we talked even more at your kichen table before I had to go home. The day after was just a normal working day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hugged and boy that felt so great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;30-07 - Date 2?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the day we started chatting over whats app after we exchanged numbers (still dont have your dutch one!) I managed to get myself another date with you after you asked me what my plans were for the evening.
I said I was going to drive around on my bike, You askes for how long my rides usually lasted. I bluffed and said an hour or 2, In the end that somehow made me end up at your kichen table once more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening we talked again like we have never met before, for hours on end until yet again it would be wise for me to leave because of work the next day. But not before I confessed I started to
like you more than a friend. You very carefully said you liked me back, and so we hugged goodbye once more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Keep me here at the bottom --&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/07/28/tinder.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/07/28/tinder.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
