<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For you my dear</title>
    <description>Just a simple site for you by my, for our adventures, and my thoughts so you may know me better.
</description>
    <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://foryoumydear.nl/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:45:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The weekend we went to Paris</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;5-10 - To France!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This lovely weekend (5-10 / 7-10) we went to Paris, we had multiple things to celebrate. First of course our second month together, And
my 28th birthday! On Friday evening I picked you up straight from work a bit too early but you managed to get to a call in the car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this we moved trough the tough traffic in the Netherlands onwards to Belgium. Over al it was a pleasant drive we stopped once at a
gas station not only to get gas, but also some food and to pee. After this quick break we went onwards to Paris where we arrived a bit too early
at the Airb&amp;amp;b you had booked for us. After some calling with our host we were she came to open up the door for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were greeted with a huge tennis hall behind the house and a interesting smell we had to go upstairs to a lovely room where we were explained
all the facilities. By this time it was around 00:00 so we went to bed to wake up the next morning to go to the inner city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;6-10 - Paris&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up and did our thing as this is our first travel together its still getting a bit used to how we are during it all.
Turns out not too bad! We were woken up by the old cat that was surprisingly loud for her age. WE did our thing got dressed got our bags and
walked out to the nearest tram station. Here we got some good old cash just in case we needed some, And faced our first minor challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610tramhalte.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Looking over the hill.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610tramhalte.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610tram.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;You in the tram.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610tram.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying the tram tickets was a bit fiddly but somehow we managed without a fight, but did end up with fresh puke under our shoes!
After this we travelled the wrong way in the tram, nothing a quick turnaround could not fix!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once at the destination of our first stop we had some lovely breakfast! which was of course a french crepe. After which it was time for museum number one! which had a main exhibition about a girl and a unicorn. Maybe its a french thing but it was way more quiet then I am used to from any
museum. But after seeing the entire place we went on to the next stop a another museum, This time about “&amp;lt;something about arabism?&amp;gt;” This was quite
a large museum divided over multiple levels of a 10 story building. The only downside was that it was mostly in french, with we both dont speak
and read so it was mainly looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it was time to explore the city itself and its hotspots. We went to sit near the Notre dame, for a lovely talk and some cuddles and ofcourse a lovely photo:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610us.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;Us looking at the Notre Dame.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610us.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;our travell map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this we went looking for the lock bridge, turnsout the cleaned it up! not to worry it was a bonus to the trip we went onwards inside the
Notre Dame where we witnessed the starting of a church session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;example-image-link&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610notredame.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;weekendparis&quot; data-title=&quot;You in the Notre Dame.&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;our-map&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/paris0610notredame.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tram halte&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We left this quite quickly and we got some delicious ice cream and ate this while looking over the river Seine. After I romantically tried to remove some ice cream from your face it was time for a quick bathroom break while we went to the Eifel tower!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once at the Eifel tower, We had to go trough a security checkpoint where we both got pooped on by a bird unfortunately, but you brought wet wipes and saved the day! After this, Yet another line to wait in this time to get the tickets to get into the tower. We wanted to take the stairs but were suddenly greeted with a closing ticket desk, Turns out that the stairs are not open to climb up after 21:00. We had to go to a different line to get the tickets for the elevator. In hind sight this was a batter idea any way But before we got there another checkpoint and up we go! time to get a great view and some lovely pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;Image here :) &amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we saw all of that we had the challenge of a hungry tummy. Which make me a bit more grumpy than it should, You compromised for me to get something quick and easy in a nice restaurant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;7-10 - Brussels and Home&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To dodododo
&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/lightbox-plus-jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/04/paris.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/10/04/paris.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The day you and I became us</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This day, In your kitchen we decided to go for our relationship.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/04/it-is-official.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://foryoumydear.nl/journey/2018/08/04/it-is-official.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Journey</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
